What?
Did Jolyne make it?
So she can go to the Discipline Cell?
Just to find that same bone
belonging to Dio? Yeah.
If I keep her safe through this,
then I plan on making her my bride.
That's the condition. Got it?
Diver, drive!
Give us your blessings.
The electrical power a
nerve carries at any given
time measures a mere seven
hundredths of a volt.
That's how little power that stand has.
Survivor's attacks make one feel
nothing, and it does nothing.
All it does is make them mad.
I don't want to say it's more time.
In all of you!
I can see where your
strengths lie from here,
your most dominant muscle
groups, and they're glorious.
Welcome to Fight Club!
Bring it on, bitches!
You know, I've just gotta say, every
one of you pisses me the hell off.
AND I'M FREAKIN' SICK OF YOU!
The enemy.
The stand user must be one of them.
Now, just a question of who.
It has to be one of them.
I'd be willing to bet it's the
one who made the guards fight.
I didn't drag my ass all
the way to this maximum
security disciplinary wing to not
get a hold of that bone. F that!
Tough shit for any stupid
chump who gets in my way, too.
Whoever it is, I don't care.
I'm gonna kill them!
Huh? What? Kill them?
Did I really just have that thought?
What's this burning, furious
emotion taking me over?
Is that fighting spirit?
The spirit that keeps on telling me
to conquer and destroy everything,
no matter who it is or what
might end up happening to me?
Is this guard really
trying to pull off the same
thing with me that he
did to the other guard?
He can't be that stupid, can he?
Fine, go ahead.
You're no match for Stone Ocean, anyway.
Stone Ocean!
Yes, I see it.
I see where your point
of strength is, FE-40536.
There's something flowing slowly from your
muscles that looks like
a thread made of liquid.
It's beautiful.
Is that the strongest power you have?
What the hell kind of move was that?
When he fought that other prisoner before,
he was bizarrely brutal and savage.
And that was just a fist fight.
But this is…
No normal humans are
capable of these moves.
That's it.
I need to beat this guard
at any cost, right now!
I can see his muscles, too.
And they look brilliant and beautiful.
Also, the way he just moved,
the agility, the power…
How can humans sustain
huge wounds like that,
then ignore that pain and fear
and still attack so viciously?
But if the intense radiance emanating from
his muscles is the marker
of his strong point,
that tells me something important.
His left leg.
I can see inside it right now.
That's the leg that I just attacked.
He must be feeling it.
That's what I sense.
And I can tell the damage
I dealt is murder for him!
Hey, Shitstain.
You get in my way, then
I'm gonna choke you out.
And now, I have to pound you!
Wait, these guys are getting into it too?
Got you!
He's a nightmare.
I need to knock this guy out already,
so I can focus on finding Dio's bone.
You almost chopped off
your own head just now.
You should be more careful.
Go to sleep, you jacked up prick!
what the my arm but what the hell just
happened shit who is this guy what
the hell have you done to me wait
that's the so this guard is a stand user
too i don't believe it this entire ward
is full of stand users with that disc
he was already granted a stand power
but i don't know what it is But still,
what exactly did he just do?
I didn't even give him the
slightest chance to fight back.
There was no sign of my stand.
There was no way he could know.
So how did he attack me?
Fuck, this is bad.
I'm losing a ton of blood.
I've never had a wound like this.
It's not like one you'd get
from any knife, razor, or blade.
I need to know what he did to me.
I still can't figure it out.
If his stand was a power type,
then I totally should have seen it.
Really?
Is that the best you can do?
Wrap your thread around me?
I can see a thread as a matter of fact.
A bundle of threads inside your body.
They're your point of strength.
It's starting to make
a bit more sense now.
But without them, you're nothing.
It's beautiful.
You're all sparkles and light.
So when did you become a stand user?
Like yesterday?
Or just now?
I see it.
There's his stand.
His stand finally appeared.
I know what he did now.
A stand user.
If he's the assassin sent to eliminate me,
then I have an idea of what I
have to do to eliminate him first.
I don't need extra power to
defend myself with threat.
A straight punch with
devastating force will
deviate significantly when
the direction is shifted,
and I'll avoid any impact.
You fell for it.
Because you used both your hands,
I was able to block your movement.
Sorry, dumbass.
That means...
And now I can stop you
and not look at your face.
Stone Ocean!
I'm putting you out of
commission for good.
What? Oh no!
No, not again.
What's doing this?
Is it a stand?
But how?
I can't see it. How can he?
Got you, bitch.
You're mine now, you
low-rent filthy pizza jet.
You dare to make fun of me
when you're the real joke here.
Who's laughing now?
Prisoners are the scum of society.
And there's nothing
that pisses me off more
than being defied by
a scum queen like you.
By the way, I felt like that the
entire time I've worked in this pit.
So don't fuck with me, lady.
I'm ready to let out all of my anger.
Get ready to take it.
Know what's about to happen?
I'm gonna snap and let all my anger out.
Let all my anger out.
Gonna let it out and feel much better.
I'm the strongest.
I'm gonna let it out.
Holy shit, the ceiling!
Oh no, that means his stand is...
No, no way.
I'm so screwed.
I need to get myself out of this now.
No, I know what his stand
power is, and here it comes.
You're done. It's over.
I've completely locked you in.
Hey, I'm a big prison guard, remember?
My job entails restraining lunatic inmates
like you every day at first glance.
It looks like my right arm is free.
But the point of this headlock
isn't only to choke you out you
understand feel that if I twist
your left shoulder joint like this?
Do you see what happens?
When I pin you like this your right
shoulder is dead and you can't raise it.
So try as you might you can't do
shit to me with your right fist!
But I'm suddenly aware this headlock
leaves part of me unguarded?
and I can't believe I'm
about to tell you what it is.
It's my balls,
which are now close to a certain right
hand that could probably crush them.
Under different circumstances,
I'd be psyched about that.
Well, I've got to keep your
grubby little hand away.
It's coming!
Shit, this is bad.
I know it stands real identity.
How am I going to get out of this?
It's the ceiling!
Look at what's happening to it.
The glass is cracking everywhere.
Fuck, it's getting worse.
I need to escape.
Stone Ocean!
I blew out his eardrum.
His grip loosened.
In the universe, there are more rocks
and dust particles than can be measured.
Many of them close enough to Earth
fall down due to its gravity.
Although most of them burn out upon
entry into the Earth's atmosphere,
if the rock itself can control and maintain
the optimum drop speed, trajectory,
and its structural integrity...
Oh, you're coming too?
Don't you worry yourself, I got it.
Not so fast, but I give the orders
and make the decisions here.
Sure, I know I asked for your assistance,
but that doesn't put you in charge.
You got that?
Oh, and by the way,
if Pale Snake is trying to eliminate
Jolene as I keep on telling you,
he may actually have sent two
assassins to the Discipline Cell.
Or maybe more.
Bet you didn't think of that.
He probably made more than three
stand users to take her out.
Now, you and I are going
to go track them down,
blow their asses off the map,
and then come straight back here.
Sound good?
Yeah, fine.
I'll be back before that guard even
starts his pre-wake-up twitching.
Don't forget,
we sealed the deal about
Jolene and I getting married,
so you'd better not
try to double-cross me.
Yeah, about that!
I still don't know what the
fuck you're talking about!
Enlighten me!
Aaaaaah!
Wait, it's a meteor!
That's the attack?
Meteors are falling towards
Earth, and directly to this guard!
That's what was attacking me!
His stand pulls down goddamn
fireball asteroids from the sky.
But they always conveniently miss
him and burn to harmless ash.
Here comes another one, like
it hurt me or something.
But before that...
I got you, and rest assured,
this time I'm not letting go.
I'm the winner, do you hear me?
I shine like a diamond.
I beat you.
I am the strongest here!
Stone ocean!
You think that's bad?
I'm about to rip the
skit off your whole body!
Let's go!
Right now, you bastard!
Let go of me!
Hey, let go!
Agh!
Man, I barely dodged getting
crushed by that thing.
I did my best to alter the meteor's path
so it would nail that crazy fuck directly.
But it did the same thing
they've all been doing.
There's not even one teeny
little scratch on that guy.
It's not fair!
When they get near him, they
just disintegrate into dust!
That guard's stand power is so intense,
he magnetizes meteors falling right
toward his body and he's fine.
I've never seen anything like it.
But, no matter what I do or how I do
it, when I have to get close to him,
somehow the only one who's in any
actual danger of getting hit is me!
Wow, this is kind of crazy.
Churns of flaming stones are crashing down
from the sky all around me everywhere.
Wait, are they meteors then?
Is that what my point of strength is?
So, F .E .40536, how many
times did you get hit, Cupcake?
Those wounds look pretty nasty.
I see both arms, your left
side, and your right leg.
Five gashes in total, or is it six?
Doesn't really matter.
The next one is going to be the
money shot, the goodnight kiss.
Huh, you serious?
Lady, you are bleeding out.
How do you even have the strength
to move right now, much less stand?
Nah, you bluffing, sister.
Any minute, your brick's on the floor.
Your arms are about as useful for
fighting as a pair of wet ankle socks.
You don't stand a chance and you know it.
I can see your muscle
tissue rotting and dying.
It's all dark like your heart.
None of them have that
brilliant sparkle like before.
What do you say we go another round?
Okay, just to see how
damaged you are, I'll bite.
Let's play. Ready?
What's wrong? Huh? Go!
Take a swing at me, I'm defenseless.
What are you waiting for?
Come and get me, Tiger.
What kind of strike you're gonna use?
Hey, maybe I should close my eyes, too.
Yes there it is that's
the bone i need the same
one that PaleSnake is
looking for i found it.
It's right over there i have to get to it
what are you doing you
can't fight anymore?
I had a feeling you'd
put your back against
the wall to shield yourself
from falling Medias!
But hey it sure did work out for me.
The Medias were already falling towards me
from the other side of the wall you lose!
I win turns out i was right
on the money that tight little
body is too wrecked to defend
my attacks and now you're gonna
die how does it go again one
prisoner sees the wall but the
other side of it is and the other
sees the stars through the bars
which one am i
there's the bone
over there if i can just get to Pale
Snake i'll do whatever it takes i
can drink filthy water i'll finally
become stronger than anyone else
of
course i'll
see the stars until
i see my father again i only want
to gaze into their fierce light.
So this is it? Good grief.
Here comes the finishing blow!
It's over!
It's gonna vaporize me.
The fatal last blow.
I can't defend myself anymore.
Not even with Stone Ocean.
I'm the strongest!
And now you're gonna die!
Not yet.
Well, you were so busy being
awesome, I took off your right boot.
Ahhhhh!
Sneaky little shit pack!
She even filled my boot
with broken pieces of brick!
Shit!
She's getting pouted!
But now taking a lot less damage?
The energy has shifted!
The meteors will burn out.
They might come close,
but they'll never hit you.
Except…
that only goes for the
meteors, right? Ah! My boot!
Good grief.
Just stop being such a drama queen.
You filthy rat and
criminal! Stone? Potion!
What?
What's wrong with her?
It's like she's never
satisfied with anything.
She refuses to give up.
It's not fair.
Now I know if something else
manages to hit the meteor first,
then it can actually get me.
I'm in horrible shit now.
How could you be so
violent, so cruel to me?
How dare you?
This bitch beat me!
Looks like I'll see the stars.
Game, set, and match!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place
other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.